(Let it go.)
=Revenge From A Wife=
=Episode 3=
Your maidenhood has been restored.
Now only the hardest step remains.
Your voice.
We need to change it.
The pain this will cause
will be several times worse
than all you've endured combined.
Hold on.
♪Devotion turns to flame♪
♪Half a life of hate and bitterness♪
♪From now on, our paths divide♪
♪The reckoning♪
(Wretch.)
(You've been dead all these years,)
(yet His Majesty still longs for you.)
Your Majesty.
You're thinking of my sister again.
Roujia has been coming to me
in my dreams every night.
Could she be reminding me
that I haven't done enough?
Your Majesty,
you built Guizhen Cottage for her
and ordered your kin to live simply.
My sister's spirit
must know
how much you miss her every day.
Only you know how to comfort me.
You and Roujia
are sisters by blood.
Whenever I see you,
it feels like
she's still here.
If I can bring Your Majesty any comfort,
it's my good fortune.
Wanniang.
Come here.
Take this.
Listen to me.
Mother!
- Mother!
(Don't worry.)
(I swear)
(I'll avenge you.)
(Medicine)
Here. This is your medicine.
Thank you, miss.
What's that smell?
Your Majesty,
(Li Dehai, Chief Palace Attendant)
that stall sells medicinal herbs.
It's been there for months.
The owner
gives free consultations
to the poor every day
and provides medicine,
all at no charge.
Word has spread,
so more people are coming.
Your Majesty,
someone so compassionate
is truly a blessing to Daxia.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The Empress's death anniversary is near.
Seeing such kindness
brings me some comfort.
(Medicine)
Xiao Che.
You've finally come.
♪Sunset fades beyond the lonely city♪
♪Dusk snow paints the green hills♪
♪A lone rider storms the old pass♪
♪Drunk, I gaze by lamplight♪
♪Old friends have all drifted away♪
♪My broken sword rusts, as do I♪
♪Jackdaws cry into the night♪
♪Half a banner snaps in the wind♪
♪In dreams, I return to the camps♪
♪Moonlight chills my armor♪
♪Life is a dream through many winters♪
♪I gaze beyond the edge of the world♪
♪Parting sorrow spills across the moon♪
♪The moon and wind mean nothing now♪
♪History turns to ash before ink dries♪
♪Who plays the zither
and sighs at the pavilion?♪
♪The past has faded away♪